指定幸存者  前情提要
Previously on Designated Survivor...
我已经被英国大使馆全职录用了
I've been posted full-time with the British embassy.
立即生效
Effective immediately.
你曾去圣卢西亚度假吗
Did you take a vacation on St. Lucia?
我和女儿每年都一起旅行一次
Every year, my daughter and I take one trip together.
今年去圣卢西亚
This year, St. Lucia.
你被弗斯特传唤了吗  因为什么
You're being subpoenaed by Foerstel? For what?
他发现了一个在圣卢西亚由埃里克·利特尔注册的银行账户
He's found a St. Lucian bank account set up by Eric Little,
六个月前  以我的名义
six months ago, in my name.
我被陷害了
I'm being set up.
利特尔被谋杀的事件调查怎么样了
Where are we with Little's murder investigation?
此时没有任何进展  先生
Nothing on that front, sir.
你能把利特尔和劳埃德联系起来么
Were you able to tie Little to Lloyd?
没有证据能够把他俩连在一起
There's no evidence that connects them.
你是切片面包出现以来最棒的
You're the greatest thing since sliced bread.
面包很棒
And bread is great.
基础性的棒  就像是水  空气  还有你
Fundamentally great. Like water. Or air. Or you.
有问题吗
Is there a problem?
从车上下来
Step out of the vehicle.
指控已经被撤了
The charges were dismissed.
但我的职责是让总统知道并没有
But my duty to inform the president wasn't.
收了一大箱信件吗
? Got a box full of letters ?
我想你也许会愿意读读
? Think you might like to read ?
这也许是你想看看的东西  但收信人写的全都是我
? Some things that you might like to see But they're all addressed to me ?
期待我有很多答复吗
? Wish I had a lotta answers ?
因为本应该那样
? 'Cause that's the way it should be ?
对于所有直接给我的问题
? For all these questions Being directed at me ?
三信日吗
Three-letter day?
每个月  白宫都能收到超过10，000封信
Every month, the White House receives 10,000 letters.
总统会选三封进行回复
The president chooses three letters to answer.
那我们应该怎么做
How does that involve us?
我们调查请求并建议总统
We investigate the requests and advise the president.
- 那可真刺激  - 是哦
- That's exciting. - Yeah.
三信日可以看作红色信件日
Three-letter day can be a red-letter day.
- 我才不干呢  - 我也是
- I'm not doing this. - For some.
我不喜欢信件  我不爱读也不爱写
I don't like letters. I don't read or write them.
- 这是哪个混蛋的主意  - 总统的
- Whose asinine idea was this? - The president's.
- 我加入  - 好样的
- I'm in. - Attaboy.
- 三信日  朋友  - 噢  给我一枪吧
- Three-letter day,amigo. - Oh, somebody please shoot me.
- 嘿  - 嗨
- Hey. - Hi.
今天不仅仅是象征性的
Today is not just simply symbolic.
在今天  我们将真正为选民服务
Today, we are gonna truly serve the electorate
通过努力回答他们的具体要问题
by trying to answer their specific requests.
亚伦和艾米莉
Aaron and Emily,
这封信是由上士丹尼尔·戈夫的寡妇写的
this was written by the widow of Daniel Goff, Sergeant First Class.
她问为什么她的丈夫被拒绝授予荣誉勋章
She asks why her husband was denied the Medal of Honor
为了他在自由与坚毅行动中的勇敢和最终牺牲
for his ultimate sacrifice and bravery during Operation Enduring Freedom.
- 在调查  - 没问题
- On it. - Absolutely.
谢谢你们
Thank you.
赛斯和里奥
Seth and Lyor,
帮助亚当森先生找出什么杀死了他的蜜蜂
help Mr. Adamson figure out what's killing his bees.
- 蜜蜂吗  - 是的  蜜蜂
- Bees? - Yes, bees.
它们是指示物种
They are an indicator species.
它们为我们80％的作物授粉
They pollinate over 80% of our crops.
它们死了  植物就会死  人类也不久就会死
They die, plants die, man will shortly follow.
尽我们所能去了解什么是杀害他的蜜蜂是符合我们利益的
It's in our interest to do what we can to find out what's killing his bees.
- 谢谢你  这是一个无上荣光  - 我确定你会做得很好的
- Thank you. This is a solemn honor. - I'm sure you'll do great.
- 头奖  - 蛇眼
- Jackpot! - Snake eyes.
肯德拉  这是一个在联邦死刑案件的赦免请求
Kendra, this is a request for a pardon in a federal death penalty case.
自2003以来没有联邦执行赦免
There hasn't been a federal execution since 2003.
他定于本星期五死于注射死刑
He's scheduled to die by lethal injection this Friday.
一封来自佛罗里达州温特黑文的匿名信
An anonymous letter from Winter Haven, Florida.
为了钱德勒·德恩寻求赦免机会吗
Seeking clemency for Chandler Dern?
他是一名药剂师  罪名是他在2001杀死了一名缉毒人员
He was a pharmacist convicted of killing a DEA agent in 2001.
写这封信的人说  德恩不服他的判决但这个人不是这样想的
This writer says that Dern appealed his sentence, but not his conviction.
这才是吸引人  很奇怪  对吗
That's what caught my eye. Strange, right?
闻所未闻  考虑到利害关系
Unheard of, given the stakes.
我不想把我的判断强加给陪审团
I'm not inclined to impose my judgment over a jury's.
但如果你发现任何东西来证明判决的不公
But if you found anything to indicate manifest injustice,
- 我愿意了解  - 我会调查的
- I would wanna know. - I'll get cracking.
你有72小时
You got 72 hours.
明白  先生  我们还有一件事
Understood. Sir, we have another issue.
你妻子的传票有了新进展  我们应该谈谈
There's been a development in regards to your wife's subpoena. We should talk.
弗斯特愿意不公开程序吗
Foerstel's offering to seal the proceedings?
有一个前提
With one condition.
那就是你不会取消传票
That you don't move to quash your subpoena.
所以这是个交易  用保密交换合作
So an inducement. Secrecy in exchange for cooperation.
如果亚历克斯出现了并且她的证词会引起刑事诉讼  这样就会公开了
If Alex appears and her answers lead to an indictment, that will go public.
这是可预见的风险
It's a calculated risk.
你把这件事解决的几率有多大
What are the odds that you can get this tossed?
抛硬币几率吧
It's a coin flip.
你的情况这样的事情是十分特殊的
The case against you is wildly circumstantial.
除非在圣卢西亚你名下的账户
With one exception. The account in St. Lucia in your name
由埃里克·利特尔开户的已经被毁了
that Eric Little opened is damning.
除非汉娜·韦尔斯可以找到那个开户的银行职员
Unless Hannah Wells can find the banker who set it up,
我都不能证明你清白
we cannot clear you.
只有银行职员能够证明
Only the banker can prove
第一夫人的圣卢西亚帐户是一个劳埃德陷阱
that the First Lady's St. Lucia account is a Lloyd set-up.
- 他们永远不会透露那个名字  - 等着看吧
- They'll never give you his name. - We'll see.
我可以是很有说服力的
I can be very persuasive.
你好  我是斯隆小姐  来这见布鲁尔先生
Hello, I'm Ms. Sloane. I'm here to see Mr. Brewer.
你想在圣卢西亚开户吗
You'd like to open an account in St. Lucia?
是的
Yes.
- 代表他人  - 是的
- On someone's behalf? - Yes.
那是我们不提供的三方服务
That is a third-party service we do not offer.
我从一位可信任的朋友那里得知
I have it from a trusted friend
你们有一位职员提供这种服务
that one of your officers does offer the service.
是这样吗
Is that so?
如果你愿意帮我和对的人连上线
If you could put me in touch with the right person,
我很乐意付你一笔额外费用
I'd be happy to pay a premium.
抱歉  我们不能帮助你
Sorry, but we are unable to help you.
如果你能告诉我这位职员的名字
If you could give me the name of the officer--
就到这里吧  日安
That will be all. Have a good day.
你不知道怎么玩枪就不要玩
Don't play with guns if you don't know how to use them.
我  知道如何玩枪
Me, I know how to use them.
你愿意给我那位职员的名字吗
Would you like to give me the name of that bank officer?
撤销是要看法官的决定
Quashing this will come down to the judge.
是的  给第一夫人一个通行证
Yes. And the optics of giving the First Lady a pass
对他们来说可能是举足轻重的事情
could weigh heavily on them.
对他们来说举足轻重的事情  是这件事真的是陷害
What should weigh heavily on them is that this is a set-up.
- 亚历克斯  - 我们决定撤销  汤姆
- Alex. - We're moving to quash, Tom.
你能给我们几分钟吗  我们得谈谈这事
Could you give us a moment? We need to discuss this.
- 是的  先生  - 谢谢你
- Yes, sir. - Thank you.
- 这场迫害已经持续几个月了  - 我知道
- This witch hunt has lasted months. - I know.
我不想给弗斯特任何喘息的机会
I don't want to give Foerstel any more oxygen.
我们利用它能利用的一切  每一个程序性的策略和战略
Every procedural maneuver, stratagem, we'll avail ourselves of all of it.
只是在推迟不可避免的事情
That's only putting off the inevitable.
弗斯特不会退缩
Foerstel won't back down
因为你引用的联邦议事规则
because you quote the  Federal Rules of Procedure.
- 这是我们唯一可行的策略  - 这是我们迄今为止所做的
- It's our only viable tactic. - It's what we've been doing so far.
打防守  然后看看我们才到哪一步
Playing defense, and look where it's gotten us.
- 更靠近悬崖  - 那我们就退后一步
- Closer to the precipice. - Then let's step back.
亚历克斯  你是位勇士
Alex, you are a fighter.
这是我爱你众多理由中的一个
It's one of the many things I love about you.
但我们不是在对抗这件事  而是在躲藏
But we're not fighting this, we're hiding.
假装这事儿就会这样过去  但它不会
Pretending like it'll blow over. It won't.
这场暴风雨已经袭击我们有一阵了
This storm has been coming at us for a while.
我们试着反转它  但没成功
We tried to outrun it, but we couldn't.
所以我们采取不同的策略  深挖这件事  勇于直面这件事
So we take a different tact, we dig in. We fight this thing.
第二季   第九集
指定
幸存者
擦枪字幕组
XGunSubTeam
原创
译制
mcar.cc
荣誉
出品
合作洽谈     Q:864413459
我今早翻身醒来你却不在了
I roll over this morning and you're not there.
翻 译   陌人不故
- 那样可会让我感到不安  - 你需要睡美容觉嘛
- That can give a guy a complex. - You needed your beauty sleep.
翻 译  Fighter
我不能帮你追踪银行职员
I could've helped you track down the banker
那个帮着陷害第一夫人的
who helped frame the First Lady.
那不是两个人的活
It wasn't a two-man job.
特 效   小螺号
你  汉娜·韦尔斯  是一匹独狼
You, Hannah Wells, are alone wolf.
追踪银行职员的名字
Who hunted down the banker's name.
翻 译   岛岛
说得对
Touché.
我们的流氓银行家有什么消息
Anything on our rogue banker?
翻 译   RossyGeng
空管局证实阿方索·朗四天前从赫瓦诺拉飞往杜勒斯
TSA confirms Alfonso Lang flew from Hewanorra to Dulles four days ago.
翻 译    云霁
他有记录么
Did he have a sheet?
校 对   Lee
有许多洗钱的指控
A lot of raps for money laundering,
但他都驳回了  否则他会被列入禁飞名单
all of which he's beaten, otherwise he'd be on the no-fly list.
你查到他的具体位置了吗
You got a 411 on his location?
只是在国际刑警组织的线人告诉我他会见了客户
Just a contact at Interpol telling me he meets with clients
在区内经常搞税务诈骗
in the district regularly to set up tax scams.
我会联系大使馆
I'll contact the embassy.
看看他是否在他们的观察名单上还触犯了底线
See if he's on one of their watch lists and tripped a wire.
圣卢西亚是英国的保护国
St. Lucia's a British protectorate.
事实上  圣卢西亚是一个主权国家  英联邦的一部分
Actually, St. Lucia's a sovereign nation. Part of the Commonwealth.
干得好  查尔斯  你应该上推理小节目了
Well done, Charles. You should go on Jeopardy!
你应该
And you should...
也去那里
Go on it, too.
嘿  肯德拉
Hey, Kendra.
当然可以  我会去的
Of course, I'll be right there.
白宫顾问有个紧急事件需要帮助
White House Counsel needs help with an urgent matter.
没问题  我一找到线索就联系你
No problem. I'll call you as soon as I find anything.
好了  表现好点  孩子们
All right. Play nice, boys.
不  我不知道是谁送的这封信
No, I don't know who sent it.
但一字一句都是对的
But every word's true. I'm innocent.
我们重审了你的档案
We reviewed your file.
你在2001年被指控谋杀了一位名叫卡尔·马利的缉毒局特工
You were convicted of murdering a DEA agent named Carl Marley in 2001.
一剂氯胺酮致死
A ketamine sting gone bad.
检察官说服陪审团
The prosecutor convinced the jury
相信你的药店有财务危机
that your pharmacy was in financial trouble.
所以就说我在黑市上卖K粉
And that I was selling ketamine on the black market
我连马路都不乱穿
when I'd never even jaywalked?
他的尸体就在你店附近的一个公园被发现
His body was found in a park near your store.
被一把没有登记过的枪射在脸上
Shot in the face with a gun that was never located.
你储藏室的地板上找到了他的血迹
Traces of his blood were found on your storage room floor.
那屋子每天有20个人进进出出  任何人都有可能带进来
Twenty people were in that room every day. Anyone could've tracked it in.
你的庭审律师呢  我们能和他谈谈吗
What about your trial lawyer? Can we talk to him?
不能了  他三年前就死了
No. He died three years ago.
他活着的时候也没啥用处
But he was pretty worthless when he was alive.
庭审之后你还剩多少钱
How much money did you have left after the trial?
事实证明  刚够上诉的钱
As it turned out, just enough to appeal the sentence.
德恩先生  这个案子情况很特殊
Mr. Dern, this was a highly circumstantial case.
你的律师不称职  我们会帮你调查这个案子
Your lawyer did a bad job. We're going to look into this for you.
太好了  但是我想我已经没有上诉的机会了
That's great. But I believe I've exhausted my appeals.
这不是上诉  这是减刑
It wouldn't be an appeal. It would be a commutation.
如果是总统批准的  我无话可说
If the president were to grant that, I wouldn't have words.
但是我期待正义太久了  从来都没等到
But I've been waiting for justice a long time, and it's never come.
希望是个可怕的东西
Hope is a dangerous thing.
我不想像一个懦夫一样祈祷永远不会来的缓刑
I don't wanna die a coward praying for a reprieve that's never coming.
这不是我想给孩子们留的榜样
That's not a legacy I want for my children.
那就别祈祷  做好准备
Then don't pray. Prepare.
剩下的交给我们
And let us do our thing.
钱德勒·德恩有两个硕士学位
Chandler Dern has two master's degrees.
一个律师  甚至是一个三脚猫律师
Does it make sense to you that a lawyer, even a crooked one,
都能说服他不上诉  这说得通吗
could convince him that it was a good idea not to appeal?
一点也说不通
Not even a little bit.
他有一个儿子在盖瑟斯堡  我们看看他有什么要说的
He has a son in Gaithersburg. Let's see what he has to say.
谢谢你与我们交谈
Thanks for talking to us.
我很高兴你们在调查我父亲的判决
I'm thrilled that you're looking into my father's sentence.
总统有可能介入吗
Is there a chance the president might step in?
这取决于我们的调查
It depends on our investigation.
我有什么能帮的
How can I help?
你觉得你父亲可能有没跟我们坦白的吗
Is there a reason your father wouldn't be forthcoming with us?
- 他跟你们说什么了  - 这不是关于他告诉我们什么
- What did he tell you? - It's not what he told us.
这是我们让你告诉我们什么
It's what we're asking you to tell us.
很有意思  你对你父亲很上心
It's interesting. You're devoted to your father.
监狱的探访日志显示你每周去那里两次
Visitor logs at the prison say you're there twice a week.
但你的妹妹  特雷西  已经16年没去看他了
But your younger sister, Tracy, hasn't been to see him in 16 years.
我们很好奇为什么
We're wondering why.
我妈妈在我6岁的时候去世了
My mom died when I was six.
父亲被抓走的时候我17岁
I was 17 when they took him away, and...
我挺过来了
I got through it.
我还开了家汽修公司
I set up an auto repair business.
特雷西就没有那么幸运了  但我父亲  他
Tracy, she wasn't so lucky. But my dad, he...
他告诉我们要把家庭放在第一位  我不想谈论特雷西
He told us to always put family first. I'm not talking about Tracy.
我们没有时间游戏了  你父亲现在命悬一线
We don't have time for games. Your father's life is on the line.
我妹妹  她经常吸毒
My sister, she's always had problems with drugs.
她经常和一些坏人一起闲逛
She used to hang out with some bad people.
我想我父亲害怕他的调查会牵连到她
I think that my father was afraid his investigation would implicate her.
这些人在你父亲的审判中作为辩护出现了吗
Were those people used as a defense in your father's trial?
没有  我父亲不让
No. My dad wouldn't allow that.
- 我们在哪能找到你妹妹  - 不能
- Where can we find your sister? -No.
要是他知道我告诉你们这些  他就不认我了
If he knew I told you any of this, he would disown me.
弗兰克  你父亲就要被判处死刑了
Frank, your father is about to be put to death.
我认为认不认你现在不是首要问题
I don't think disowning you is the issue here.
你丈夫很帅  戈夫夫人
Your husband was very handsome, Mrs. Goff.
谢谢
Thank you.
丹尼尔是我的全部
Daniel was my everything.
总统被你的信感动了  你能再多告诉我们点吗
The president was moved by your letter. Could you tell us more?
丹尼尔在2013年被派往坎大哈  对战伊斯兰国
Daniel was sent to Kandahar in 2013 to battle ISIL.
国际维和部队的一部分
Part of the international peacekeeping force.
是的  首批美国伤亡人员之一
Yes. One of the first American casualties.
在他的葬礼上  他的一个士兵  曼凯维奇下士告诉我
At his funeral, one of his soldiers, Corporal Mankiewicz, told me
丹尼尔单枪匹马地把叛乱分子挡在海湾  直到救援到达
Daniel single-handedly kept the insurgents at bay until help could arrive.
他阻止他们越过美国的阵地
He stopped them from overrunning the American position.
-  这听起来非常英勇  - 我也这么认为
- That sounds like conspicuous bravery. -I think so.
但是我写给他的上司  陆军上校
But I wrote his CO, Colonel Baines...
他没有理我
And he ignored me.
过去四年  我写了12封信  他一封都没回
Twelve letters over the past four years, and he didn't answer one.
丹尼尔曾经告诉我特种部队就像家人一样
Daniel once told me Special Forces was like family,
但是这不是对待家人的方式
but this is not how you treat family.
我们的儿子  小丹尼  现在7岁了
Our son, Danny Junior, is seven now.
问起他的爸爸
Asking about his father.
我想告诉他  他的父亲是一名战争英雄
I would like to tell him his dad was a war hero,
不是死在几万公里之外的某个陌生人
not just some stranger who died 10,000 miles away.
我们代表总统  向您承诺会调查这件事情
On behalf of the president, we promise to look into this.
谢谢你们
Thank you.
戈夫中士的部队在坎大哈遭到伏击
Sergeant Goff's unit was ambushed in Kandahar.
迫击炮  流弹  机枪  他们被困了几个小时
Mortars. RPGs. Machine guns. They were pinned down for hours.
伤亡惨重
Took a lot of casualties.
听起来能活下来的都应该得块奖章
It sounds you deserve a medal for even coming through that.
我同意  但戈夫不在那里
I agree. But Goff wasn't there.
他在哪
Where was he?
他在喀布尔德瓦扎区进行侦察
He was doing recon in the Kabul Dwarza district.
他离开了  就是在这  简易爆炸装置取走了他的性命
It's a click away, that's where the IED took him out.
你向戈夫中士的遗孀解释这个问题了吗
Did you explain this to Sergeant Goff's widow?
好多次了  但她还是坚持写信
Repeatedly. But she kept writing.
她不是第一个想要自己的丈夫被认可的遗孀
She is not the first widow that wants recognition for her husband,
但事实就是事实
but facts are facts.
经历过几次之后  我就不再回应了
After some time, I had to stop responding.
- 还有其他目击者吗  - 只有曼凯维奇下士
- Were there any other witnesses? - Just Corporal Mankiewicz.
他给了她奖章的念头
He put the idea of a medal in her ear.
- 曼凯维奇现在在哪  - 他死了  先生
- So where's Mankiewicz now? - He's dead, sir.
他服役期满一年后自杀了
He committed suicide a year after leaving the service.
根据这些  他是唯一潜在的目击者了
According to this, he was the only potential witness left.
我想是这样的
I guess that's that.
- 迈克  你想补充点什么吗  - 这不合规矩  长官
- Mike, you wanna add something? - It's not appropriate, sir.
- 如果是我问你呢  - 只是
- It is if I'm asking. - It's just...
那是戈夫的部队
That was Goff's unit.
如果他们正在和敌人对峙的话
It doesn't make sense he'd be a click away from his men
他没有理由扔下自己的部队离开
if they were expecting hostiles, which they would've been.
你觉得陆军上校搞错了
You think Colonel Baines is mistaken.
这只是我的观点  长官
In my opinion, sir.
迈克在特种部队服役了六年
Mike served six years, Special Forces.
如果他认为没有要补充的  就没有要补充的了
If he doesn't think something's adding up, something's not adding up.
- 继续挖掘  - 是的长官
- Dig deeper. -Yes, sir.
- 艾米莉  我能耽误一会儿吗  - 当然可以  长官
- Emily, can I borrow you? -Of course, sir.
他们这周一直在鼓吹这个
They've been banging the drum on this all week.
媒体注意到了
The media's picked it up.
这就是弗斯特试图诱使亚历克斯现在作证的原因
That's why Foerstel's trying to induce Alex to testify now.
他知道热度在上升
He knows the heat's turning up.
他正试图利用时机优势
He's trying to take advantage of the timing.
我今天从他办公室得到一个消息
I got a message from his office today.
他有辛辛那提地区警方虐待调查的最新情况
He has an update on the Cincinnati area police abuse investigation.
为什么  这已经休眠好几个月了
Why? That's been dormant for months.
- 我知道  时机太奇怪了  - 不  一点也不奇怪
- I know. The timing's odd. - No, it's not.
他想谈谈我妻子传唤的记录
He wants to talk off the record about my wife's subpoena.
这就是为什么他联系你而不是肯德拉
That's why he contacted you instead of Kendra.
- 你要我跟他见见吗  - 是的
- Do you want me to take the meeting? - Yes.
他一谈到伊卡洛斯  你就赶紧离开
The second he talks about Icarus, walk away.
我不希望这个办公室有
I don't want this office to have the slightest appearance
任何妨碍调查的痕迹
of trying to obstruct this investigation.
- 明白  - 谢谢你
- Understood. - Thank you.
- 主管先生  - 谢谢你见我
- Mr. Director. - Thanks for meeting me.
你有辛辛那提调查的最新情况
You have an update on the Cincinnati investigation?
是的  我的意见是可能存在不法行为
Yes. My considered opinion is there may have been wrongdoing.
严重的不法行为
Serious wrongdoing.
我们的观点是  到现在为止  现有的事实并不能支持这一结论
And our opinion is that the facts to date don't remotely support that conclusion.
这是临时意见  这也是为什么调查还要继续下去
It's provisional opinion, which is why an investigation has to continue.
一个什么样的客观观察者
Despite the fact you're chasing
会不管你正在追查的事实而含沙射影
what any objective observer would describe as innuendo.
狂野的阴谋论
Wild conspiracy theories.
所有的调查都会追踪事实  直到披露事情的真相
All investigations chase those things until they disclose the truth.
或者什么也证明不了
Or turn up nothing.
同时  对你正在调查的人也会造成损害
Meanwhile, damage is done to those you're investigating.
如果调查对象是无辜的  他们不会有任何损害
If the subjects of this investigation are innocent, there won't be any damage.
我们都知道这不是事实
We both know that's not true.
声誉可能受到伤害  机构会受到侵蚀
Reputations can be harmed. Institutions eroded.
这不是我要关心的
That's not my concern.
这是你想让我告诉总统的吗
Is that what you want me to tell the president?
告诉他辛辛那提不是个人的  这是专业
Tell him Cincinnati is not personal. It's professional.
而且我有责任让美国人民跟沿着这条道路走到最后
And I owe a duty to the American people to follow this to the end of the line.
不管是什么
No matter what.
弗斯特想强调他不会屈服
Foerstel wanted to underscore he wouldn't stand down.
- 没想到他会这样  - 这就是为什么
- Didn't think he would. - And here's why.
媒体报道了伊卡洛斯调查
The media's covering the Icarus investigation.
他把自己的职业声誉赌在结果上了
He's staking his professional credibility on the outcome.
如果你是一名职业公务员  这不成问题
Not a problem if you're a career civil servant.
问题是他是
Which he is.
不会长远的  我有预感  长官
Not for long. I played a hunch, sir.
我在奥尔巴尼找到了他的消息来源  事实证明
I reached out to a source in Albany, where he's from, and it turns out,
就在伊卡洛斯调查开始的时候
he formed an exploratory committee for a 2018 New York Senate run,
他组建了一个2018年纽约参议院的探索委员会
right when the Icarus investigation began.
他也有一个秘密的政治行动委员会
He has a secret PAC in the works, too.
他们已经筹集了50万美元
They've already raised half a million dollars.
他正在调查案子的背景
He's doing it on the back of the investigation.
我们知道你注重过程
We know you respect process,
所以我们建议你指定一个特别检察官来调查
so we're recommending you appoint a special prosecutor to investigate.
- 一位特别检察官吗  - 是的 先生
-A special prosecutor? -Yes, sir.
这并不会结束伊卡洛斯一案的调查
It doesn't end the Icarus investigation.
只是单纯的把弗斯特剔出去
It simply removes Foerstel from the equation.
鉴于他可能居心叵测
Which is in the best interest of the White House
这样是对白宫最好的方式
since he may have ulterior motives.
有抱负并不是居心叵测
Ambition is not an ulterior motive.
这只是在这里生存的必备副产品罢了
It's a by-product of the work that gets done in this town
没人可以避免
and no one's immune.
- 作为总统我也一样  - 先生
-Present company included. -Sir--
关于特别检察官一事
With regards to a special prosecutor,
以往的经验说明事情会一发不可收拾
history tells me that they're runaway trains.
调查一个接一个  如此往复
One investigation turns into another, etcetera.
太过冒险了
Way too risky.
这是两害取其轻  我们可以承担这个风险
It's the lesser of two evils. A risk we can manage.
艾米莉  我明白
Emily, I get it.
我会仔细考虑的  谢谢
I'll take it under advisement. Thank you.
谢谢您  总统先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
三信日  是吧
Hey, so three-letter day, huh?
对  三信日
Yeah. Three-letter day.
等等  我能跟你说几句话吗
Wait, hang on. Um, can I talk to you?
我有点事
Uh, I've got a thing I...
听着  我也有事
Look, um, I have a thing, too, okay?
如履薄冰
It's called walking on eggshells,
这就是我过去几天的状态
which is what I feel like I've been doing the last few days.
我很好奇我帮我哥哥隐藏毒品被抓的事情
I'm wondering if you told the president that I got arrested
你告诉总统了没有  这对我很重要
for covering up my brother's drugs, and what that means for me.
因为我也是很注重就业保障的人
Because I'm also obsessed with this thing called job security.
事态在升级
It's an evolving situation.
升级  知道了
"Evolving." Got it.
是
Yeah.
那也是一个问题
That's also a thing.
蜜蜂大全
趣味小知识  蜂群一次培养出很多蜂后
Interesting fact. A colony rears several queens at once.
第一只受孕排卵的蜂后会在蜂巢内把其他蜂后都扎死
The first queen that hatches stings the others to death in their cells.
如果两只同时排卵  他们会以死决胜负
If two emerge at once, they fight until one is killed.
就好像选举一样
It's just like an elections.
我本来不是要当养蜂人的
I didn't set out to be an apiarist.
一开始只是爱好  不知不觉  我有了三个蜂巢
It began as a hobby, and before I knew it, I had three colonies.
那他们的维护肯定要花不少时间
Their upkeep must take a lot of time.
是  但我现在每月能从我的蜂巢中获利价值4000美元的蜂蜜
Yes. But I now harvest $4,000 a month worth of honey from my hives.
很厉害  我们需要怎么帮你
That's excellent. So, how can we help?
埃迪相信联邦航空局正在杀掉我们的蜜蜂
Eddie thinks the FAA is killing our bees.
是吗  如何杀掉
Really? How?
那个监控空中航线的雷达设施
That new Air Route Surveillance Radar facility,
大约就是在我的蜜蜂们灭绝的时候开始启用的
it opened around the time of the die-off.
蜜蜂通过磁场找寻方向
Bees navigate using magnetic fields.
雷达会变成一种干扰
I think the radar is disrupting that.
他们是飞的撞树上了吗
Are they flying into trees?
不  赛斯  他们是昆虫  不是弱智
No, Seth. They're insects, not imbeciles.
他们使用太阳罗盘来导航
They use a solar compass to navigate.
一旦被干扰  相当于破坏了他们的空间记忆
Disrupt that, you compromise their spatial memory.
无法找到食物
They can't find their food.
你看来是个蜂类专家啊
You must be a fellow melittologist.
稍有涉猎  你跟航路监控雷达那边谈过了吗
I dabble. So you've spoken with the ARSR?
谈过了  我告诉他们我三个蜂群中的两个都被彻底消灭了
Yes. I told them two of my three colonies had been completely wiped out.
但他们无视我  所以我才给总统写了信
But they ignored me. That's why I wrote the president a letter.
- 埃迪非常有主动性  - 白宫亦如此
-Eddie's very proactive. -So is the White House.
我们不想给你们添麻烦的
Oh, we didn't mean to put you to all this trouble.
不会  有麻烦的是联邦航空局
Oh, no. The trouble will be the FAA's.
让东方蜜蜂原地待命  救援在路上了
Tell  Apis cerana  to stand by. Help's on the way.
再联络
Uh, we'll be in touch.
有趣的小知识
Interesting fact.
- 蜜蜂从不睡觉的  - 关我什么事
-Bees never sleep. -I don't care.
他们是唯一为人类制造食物的昆虫
They're the only insect that produces food for humans.
跟我有什么关系吗
I still don't care.
你被蛰过  不是吗
Oh, you've been stung, haven't you?
斯莱特先生
Hey, Ms. Slater.
我是赛斯·怀特  这位是里奥·布恩  感谢您的到来
Seth Wright. This is Lyor Boone. Thank you so much for coming.
对于总统对航天事业的兴趣  我局非常激动
On behalf of the FAA, we're thrilled the president has an interest in aviation.
那倒没有  他只是对蜜蜂感兴趣而已
Oh, he doesn't. His interest is in bees.
- 天  不会又是那个叫埃迪的吧  - 你记得他吗
-Oh, God. Not that Eddie guy again. -You remember him?
作为航线检测雷达部的负责人  我差点要申请一个针对他的限制令
As the administrator of the ARSR, I have a hard time forgetting someone
这种人我怎么可能会忘记
I nearly got a restraining order against.
- 信件  电话  纠察队  - 你全部当做没看见
-The letters. The calls. The pickets. -All of which you ignored.
不是的
No, we didn't.
我们试图达成友好一致的解决办法  但问题自己解决掉了
We tried to reach an amicable settlement, but the problem resolved itself.
至少我以为是这样的额
Or I thought it did.
- 谁告诉你的  - 海伦·艾德森
-Who told you that? -Helen Adamson.
他妻子啊
His wife?
是她  钱德勒的女儿
That's her. Chandler's daughter.
德恩夫人  我也是汉娜  联邦调查局的
Ms. Dern? I'm Hannah Wells. FBI.
这位是肯德拉·戴恩斯  白宫顾问
This is Kendra Daynes. The White House Counsel.
- 我给你留了留言  - 我没什么好说的
-I've left you messages. -I've nothing to say.
是关于你父亲的  你还记得他  不是吗
It's about your dad. You remember him, don't you?
温特黑文  滑雪者的天堂
温特黑文  你在那里呆了蛮久啊
Winter Haven? You spend a lot of time there?
麻烦不要打扰我
Please leave me alone.
- 是你就你父亲的事情给我们写信得嘛  - 不是
-Did you write to us about your Dad? -No.
崔西  我们是为白宫工作的  如果你父亲真的清白  我们可以救他
Tracy We work for the White House. If your Dad is innocent, we can save him.
如果你知道任何可以帮助我们证明
If you know something that can help us prove--
我不知道  请让我走吧
I don't. Now please, let me go.
她都不敢直视我们
She couldn't even look us in the eye.
可能是于心有愧  我们分析一下
Could be a guilty conscience. but let's play it out.
她年轻的时候吸过毒
She's a strung-out teen back in the day.
莫名其妙掺和到克他命交易里  中间人死了
somehow got mixed up in the ketamine buy. The agent's death.
他父亲替她顶了罪
Her dad takes the fall for her.
就在他父亲临死前  她屈服了
When he's looking at his last meal, she finally caves.
写了信来挽救父亲的生命
Writes a letter to save his life.
我看看她有没有前科记录  贩毒定罪
I'll see if she has a rap sheet, prior drug convictions.
好了  我得去和代理瑞内特见面讨论第一夫人的案子了
Okay. I have to meet Agent Rennett about the First Lady's case.
一小时之后白宫见吧
See you in the White House in an hour?
- 一有消息我就通知你  - 好
-I'll call as soon as I hear something. -Okay.
来了
Hey.
- 你今天挺神秘啊 - 对  三信日嘛
-You've been scarce. -Yeah, it's three-letter day.
这是某种邮政节日吗
Is that some sort of postal holiday?
不是  银行家那里查到了什么
No, it's... What do we have on the banker?
朗先生有双重国籍
Our Mr. Lang has dual citizenship.
同时持有圣卢西亚和英国护照
St. Lucia and the UK. Multiple passports.
他是使用圣卢西亚护照落地美国的
He landed here using his St. Lucia passport.
几天前用英国护照去了加拿大
Used his British one to pass into Canada a few days ago.
鉴于他对双重身份的滥用  我们无法及时抓到他
He's exploiting multiple identities so we can't catch him in real time.
真是赶在银行业立法者前头的好方法
Good way to stay one step ahead of the banking regulators.
等我们的系统更新出他的信息  他可能都跑到加德满都去了
By the time our systems update, he could be in Kathmandu.
我们必须找到他
We have to find him.
他是避免第一夫人不被FBI询问的最后希望了
He's the First Lady's last hope to avoid the FBI inquiry.
喂
Yeah.
阿方索·朗在乔治城有所公寓
Alfonso Lang has a condo in Georgetown
他是从一家叫做蒙特拉特联盟的寡头控股公司那里租的
he leases through a closely held corporation called Montserrat Alliance.
我把地址发给你
I'm texting you the address.
我们都无法确认他在不在美国
We don't know that he's in the country.
我可以确认  我查到了公司信用卡一个半小时以前的消费记录
I do. I can trace a purchase to a company credit card 90 minutes ago.
- 在杜邦的一家按摩妓院  - 谢了  查克
-A massage parlor in Dupont. -Thanks, Chuck.
朗在本地  查克马上把具体信息发给我们
Lang's local. Chuck is texting us the deets.
如果我们能让朗坦白  他是为埃劳德办事
If we can get Lang to confess that he was working at Lloyd's behest
制造了第一夫人从伊卡洛斯那里受贿的假象
to make it look like the First Lady was getting a payola from Icarus,
我们就可以还她清白
we can clear her name.
好  我去上个厕所  等下见
Great. I'm gonna hit the loo. I'll see you in a second.
你记得部分车牌吗
You got a partial plate?
前三个字母  查克在查了
First three letters. Chuck's running it.
- 这是宝贵的一课啊  - 什么
-There's a lesson here. -What's that?
你不应该单挑银行家
You shouldn't beat up bankers without me.
尤其是想要陷害第一夫人的银行家
Especially bankers who want to frame the First Lady.
你觉得是你的话躲得开那辆车吗
You think you could've gotten out of the way of that car?
不  但我会在他上车前就打到他的
Nope. I would've shot the guy before he got in it.
朗先生  汉娜·威尔斯  联邦调查局的
Mr. Lang? Hannah Wells. FBI.
电视开着呢
TV's on.
你确定不是某人在求救吗
You sure that's not someone calling for help?
紧急情况  不需要搜捕令
Exigent circumstances. No need for a warrant.
你确实在这里呆了蛮久
You really have been here too long.
但不如我久
I've been here longer.
有人吗
Hello?
朗先生
Mr. Lang?
他刚走
We just missed him.
有人给他报信了
Someone tipped him off.
贝恩斯上校  我们还有一些关于坎大哈的问题
Colonel Baines, we have more questions about Kandahar.
这些是戈夫中士打仗时
Those are the GPS coordinates of Sergeant Goff's phone
被杀位置所显示的手机GPS坐标
during the battle in which he was killed.
你知道这些坐标有趣在哪里吗
You know what's interesting about these coordinates?
他们把戈夫中士放在战场中央
They put Sergeant Goff in the middle of the battle,
距离侦查地点很近
not a click away doing recon.
我了解的信息就是这样的
That's the information I had.
那我现在来给你看看我们了解的信息
Let me show you the information we have.
这是一份离婚申请  你的离婚申请
This is a divorce filing. Your divorce filing.
离婚理由写的是通奸
And it lists adultery as the grounds.
你妻子和戈夫中士的婚外情
An affair your wife had with Sergeant Goff.
提交有误材料是对军事法庭的藐视
Filing a false report is a court-martial offense.
开除军籍  坐牢服刑  这些都不用我说了吧
Dishonorable discharge. Prison time. I don't need to tell you that.
不用
No, you don't.
所以你要对戈夫中士的行为重新陈述
So you will amend your statement of Sergeant Goff's conduct.
而且你要推荐他为国牺牲值得获得荣誉勋章
And you'll recommend that he be posthumously awarded the Medal of Honor.
好
Okay.
我会的
I'll do that.
谢谢
Thank you.
我不会遗漏任何一个
And I won't leave out any of it.
不仅是因为他背叛了我的信任
Not how he betrayed my trust.
引诱我的妻子  毁了我的婚姻  或是种种行为
Or seduced my wife. Or ruined my marriage, or any of it.
他的遗孀可以把我的证词挂在他的荣誉勋章旁
And his widow can frame my statement right next to his Medal of Honor.
这么说来你们不同意问候戈夫军士
So both of you disagree with regards to Sergeant Goff?
是的  我们一致认为他的英勇应该被认可
Yes. We both agree he should be recognized for his valor.
但是勋章是给生者的  并非亡者  勋章慰藉人心
But medals are for the living, not the dead. They provide comfort.
如果我们把勋章颁给戈夫军士的话
If we award this medal to Sergeant Goff,
他的妻子也将知道他的不忠
his wife will also learn about his infidelity.
我不同意
And I disagree.
这些调查的关注点太局限  都靠战场上的事实来决定
These inquiries have a narrow focus, to determine the facts on the battlefield.
哪些是值得赞扬的功勋
Which deserve commendation.
没错  一旦你把外来人员的情况考虑进来
Yes. Once you factor extraneous personal circumstances into the mix--
勋章就是关于外来人员情况的
The medal is about extraneous personal circumstances.
那它对于近亲属又将意味着什么
What it will mean to the next of kin.
我们能给予近亲属最好的礼物便是真相
The greatest gift we can give the next of kin is the truth.
我想见见戈夫夫人和她的儿子  就在总统办公室这里
I would like to meet with Mrs. Goff and her son, here in the Oval Office.
当然可以
Absolutely.
我可以提一下另一件事吗
May I address another matter?
可以  说吧
Sure, what is it?
我来这是拥护透明制度的
I'm here championing for transparency.
我愧于承认我没能像您一样坦率透明
I'm ashamed to admit I haven't been as transparent with you
我本该处理好个人问题的
as I should have been regarding a personnel issue.
请继续
I'm listening.
几年前  赛斯被捕控告
A few days ago, Seth was arrested and charged--
我知道这件事的
I already know about it.
您知道
You do?
哥伦比亚地区检察官是我的朋友  我们一起打牌
The District of Columbia DA is a friend. We play cards together.
我一从喀布尔回来他就告诉我了
He told me as soon as I got back from Kabul.
很抱歉我没及时讨论这个问题
I'm sorry we didn't have this conversation sooner.
我也是
So am I.
重点是  我们正待面临
The point is, we're having it now.
我也知道白宫是个大家庭
I know that the White House is like a family.
我想象不到这有时对你来说有多难
I can't imagine how difficult it is for you sometimes
与大家在同一个战壕里
in the trenches with everyone.
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
但你为我效力
But you work for me
我在暗处是无法工作的
and I can't do my job when I'm kept in the dark.
我依靠你就这类问题上进尽忠言
I rely on you to counsel me through these kinds of matters.
我明白
Understood.
说到这里
Having said that...
处理赛斯这件事你有什么想法
What do you think I should do about Seth?
看他们  多么单纯  又脆弱
Look at them. So innocent. So vulnerable.
它们只是蜜蜂  里奥
They're bees, Lyor.
等等  里奥  等一下
Wait, Lyor, hold on.
控诉  海伦阿达姆松  正义必须被维护
J'accuse,  Helen Adamson. Justice must be done.
等等  等等  里奥  放松点
Wait, wait. Lyor, relax.
我很放松
I am relaxed.
放松的就像要安慰一个女人
Relaxed as someone about to confront a woman over apicide can be.
- 这不是个词  - 是的  的确
-That's not a word. -Yes, it is.
- 我们不知道她杀了那些蜜蜂  - 是啊
-We don't know that she killed the bees. -Yes, we do.
- 你不能再按铃了  - 对 不按了
-You have to stop ringing the bell. -No, I don't.
抱歉  刚从浴室出来
Sorry. Just got out of the shower.
我们需要谈谈了
We need to talk.
- 好  好吧  艾迪不在  - 不 就咱们三个
-Oh, okay. Eddie stepped out. -Oh, just the three of us, then.
等您方便了我们可以什么时候再回来  谢谢
We can come back at a more convenient time. Thanks.
等我一下就好了  请进
I'll just be a minute. Come in.
很好
Great.
请自便  我稍后回来
Make yourselves comfortable and I'll be right back.
- 谢谢  - 感谢
-Thank you. - Thanks.
你要干什么
What are you doing?
喂
Hey.
你知道这给了我更多证据
You realize this gives me more evidence
就因为你无意中的承诺
for your involuntary commitment application?
她杀了那些蜜蜂 成百上千
She killed the bees. Thousands of them.
- 不是她  是空管局干的 - 错
-She didn't. The FAA did. -Wrong.
三分之二的蜂群患上衰竭失调症
Two of the three colonies collapsed completely.
剩下三分之一还算完好
The third seems to be fine.
也就是说  雷达使它们变弱
Which means that while the radar may have weakened them,
她发出了致命一击
she applied the coup de grace.
就是这个
And this was it.
海伦阿达姆森就是蜂群衰竭失调症
Helen Adamson is the colony collapse disorder.
好吧  动物星球  慢点讲让我懂
Okay, Animal Planet. Slow down and take me through it.
这是蜂王浆  很多
This is royal jelly. A massive amount.
你从蜂房中拿走太多 蜂后就不产卵了
You take too much from the hive, the queen stops laying.
幼虫逐渐死亡
The larvae starts dying.
- 为什么她要害死蜜蜂  - 嫉妒
-Why would she kill the bees? - Jealousy.
你看这房子  对蜜蜂来说简直是圣殿
Have you seen the house? It's a glorious shrine to bees.
她摆脱了蜜蜂  就挽回她丈夫了
She gets rid of the bees, she gets her husband back?
是的  除非  他知道她是个连环杀手  并打算离开她
Yes. Except, he's going to leave when he learns she's a serial killer.
他一无所知
He's not learning anything.
我们的任务是拯救蜜蜂  不是破坏他们的婚姻
Our remit is to save the bees, not wreck their marriage.
我会拯救蜜蜂的  通过破坏她们的婚姻
We'll save the bees by wrecking the marriage.
不  不要  听好  我有个计划  好吗
No, no. Listen, I have a plan, okay?
我会拯救你的蜜蜂
It'll save your bees,
并且从情感诉讼的疏远中拯救联邦政府
and the federal government from an alienation of affection lawsuit.
现在  坐下  闭嘴听我解释
Now, sit down, shut up and let me explain.
为什么人们叫它椭圆办公室
Why do they call it the Oval Office?
因为它的形状是椭圆的
Because it's shaped like an oval.
什么是椭圆形
What's an oval?
形似圆  但压扁了
Sort of like a circle, but squished.
这还有三角办公室吗
Is there a triangle office?
- 丹尼  问题够多了  - 不  没关系的
-Danny, that's enough questions. -No, it's fine.
这没有  要是有的话一定很酷
There isn't, but it would be really cool if there was.
我们坐下说吧
Why don't we have a seat?
戈夫太太 我深表歉意
Mrs. Goff, I am very sorry,
我并不能授予您先生勋章
but I am not gonna be able to present your husband with the medal.
我们的调查没有结果
Our investigation was inconclusive.
记忆会淡化  证据会消失
Memories fade. Witnesses disappear.
这样的例子太多太多了
There's a high standard of proof for this sort of thing.
我明白  先生
I understand, sir.
我今日请您二位来此
I asked you both here today
因为我想亲自赠与您这个
because I wanted to present you with this, from me.
我还想和你说说话  丹尼
And I wanted to talk to you, Danny.
说说你的父亲
About your father.
好的
Okay.
我想让你知道他有多么英勇
I want you to know how brave he was.
是你父亲的牺牲换来了更多人的生命
There are people alive today because of what your father did.
他因此成为英雄
That's what made him a hero.
我爸爸很勇敢的
My dad was brave.
是的  他非常勇敢
Yes, he was. Very.
要是有人问你怎么知道的
And if anyone asks you how you know that,
你就告诉他们美国总统说的
tell them that the president of the United States told you.
谢谢您
Thank you.
不  是我感激你们
No. Thank you.
我们很高兴空管局同意重新寄送无线电波
We are pleased to report that the FAA has agreed to redirect its radio waves
这样你的蜂群就不再受影响了
so that your colonies are no longer affected.
- 真的吗  - 是的
-Really? -Yes.
我们期待着你们的蜂群数量回升
So we anticipate a resurgence in your bee population.
强势复活
A robust resurgence.
你看 海伦 我就说过总统先生会关心的
See, Helen. I told you President Kirkman cared.
你敢感谢的人是你妻子
The person you should be thanking is your wife.
是她让空管局竭尽全力
She's the one who brought the FAA to heel.
- 我不知该说什么好  - 我就不打扰你们了
-I don't know what to say. -We'll let you say it in private.
不  等等
No, wait.
我为我的行为感到羞耻
I'm ashamed of my behavior.
我以背叛来对待我妻子的爱
I've repaid my wife's devotion with treachery.
我要当各位的面坦白
I wanna confess it in front of everyone here.
- 艾迪  - 我们该走了 里奥
-Eddie? -We should go, Lyor.
- 你的玫瑰  被鹿吃了的  - 怎么样了
-Your roses? The ones the deer ate? -What about them?
- 不是鹿吃的  我毒死了它们  - 什么
-It wasn't the deer. I poisoned them. -What?
- 走吧 里奥  - 你真无礼
- Now, Lyor. -You're being rude.
他想要卸下重负
He wants to unburden himself.
他们想把它从食物那引开
They were drawing them away from better food sources.
我真是鬼迷心窍了  我十分抱歉
I was desperate. Oh, God, I am so sorry.
我也很抱歉  我没有杀光那些寄生虫
I am sorry, too. That I didn't kill more of those parasites.
- 你杀了我的蜜蜂  - 杀的还不够多  你个混蛋
-You killed my bees? -Not enough of them, you bastard.
- 凶手  - 你才是凶手
- You murderer! -You're the murderer!
- 现在可以走了  - 我妈说的真对
-Now we can go. - My mother was right about you!
真想杀了她
Oh, speaking of someone I wanna kill.
你胆敢提她的名字
Don't you dare mention her name.
我真该嫁给兰斯波顿逊
I should have married Lance Burtleson.
兰斯  你倒是嫁啊
Lance? Please!
有人想要撞倒你
Someone tried to run you down?
是职业风险  我还好 和我说说话
It's an occupational hazard. I'm fine. Talk to me.
我在系统中查了查特蕾西
I checked Tracy in the system.
无记录  不过我从另一个德恩身上找到了线索
No record. But I got a hit from another Dern.
- 她的兄弟  弗兰克  -什么罪名
- Her brother, Frank. -What's his collar for?
2001年 毒品罪
Drug conviction in 2001.
在他父亲犯罪的六个月后
Six months after his dad's conviction.
不良行为罪和持有麻醉品罪
Misdemeanor and possession of ketamine.
是当年一种稀有的致幻药
Which was a rare designer drug back in 2001.
有没有可能钱德勒德恩是在包庇什么人
Meaning if Chandler Dern was covering for someone,
不是他女儿
it wasn't his daughter.
- 互相传个话  - 好的
-Keep each other posted. -Deal.
总统要特赦我吗
Is the president going to pardon me?
除非你说真话
Not unless you tell the truth.
我说了16年真话  我是清白的
I've been telling the truth for 16 years. I'm innocent.
我相信你
I believe you.
我还相信你知道谁是有罪的
And I also believe you know who's not.
这是弗兰克的逮捕笔录
This is Frank's arrest record.
这之间有什么关系吗
What does that have to do with anything?
我们都知道那天晚上发生了什么
We both know what happened that night.
你的儿子想买麻醉剂  但事情出差错了  他就杀了卡尔·马利
Your son tried to buy ketamine. It went wrong. He killed Carl Marley.
那不是真的
That's a lie.
你做了替罪羊  让你的女儿保密
You took the fall. And made your daughter keep the secret.
这件事让她崩溃
And it destroyed her.
但她还是遵你所言
But she kept faith with you.
直到她再也忍不下去  因为她不想眼看着她父亲送命
Until she couldn't anymore because she didn't wanna watch her father die.
如果你认为我会放弃我的儿子  你肯定不曾有过孩子
If you think I'm gonna give up my son, you must not have children.
你已被宣判为有罪
You've been tried and convicted for this crime.
没有检察官会因此而指控弗兰克
No prosecutor on Earth will try to charge Frank for this now,
更不会说服陪审团判他有罪了
let alone try to convince a jury to convict him.
但人们会知道的
But the world will know.
邓恩先生  如果你想让总统赦免你
Mr. Dern, if you want the president to pardon you,
他需要从你嘴里听到真相
he needs to hear the truth from your lips.
我最后悔的就是对特蕾西造成的伤害
I regret the damage done to Tracy more than anything.
如果我的死能让她再次圆满  那我死而无憾
And I would gladly die if it would make her whole again.
但我现在帮不了她
But I can't help her now.
我能救弗兰克
I can help Frank.
他还有大好人生  我愿意牺牲自己来保住他
He has a life. And I will sacrifice mine so that he can keep his.
警卫
Guard!
就一小会儿
This will just take a second.
我已决定向总统提出辞呈
I've decided to offer the president my resignation.
什么
What?
前两天我一直躲在这里
I've been skulking around here the last two days.
我知道他清楚我被捕了
I know he knows I've been arrested.
我能从他看我的眼神里看出来
I can see it in the way he looks at me.
从他说话语气里听出来  他让我去查看蜜蜂
I can hear it in his tone. He put me on bee patrol.
他向来关注蜜蜂
He cares about bees.
和里尔一起查看
Bee patrol with Lyor.
我被弃如敝履  却不知该怎么办
I'm in the doghouse. I don't know how to get out.
所以我想向他提交辞呈
So I figure I'll offer him my resignation.
如果他同意了  那很好  不然的话
If he accepts, I know I'm good. If not--
- 他不会同意的  - 你怎么知道
- He won't accept it. - How do you know that?
因为我建议他辞掉你  他拒绝了
Because I told him to fire you. And he declined.
- 我不得不客观一些  - 我明白
- I had to be objective. - No, I know.
客观来讲我认为你的行为是不忠诚的
An objective Emily would view your behavior as disloyal.
你向一个绝不能妥协的人做出了妥协
You compromised the one person you can't compromise.
- 而且是出于自愿  - 我明白
- And you did it willingly. - I know.
并且你向我做出了让步
And you compromised me.
事情发生后  我从各个角度去看待这件事
And I've looked at this every which way since it's gone down.
重新考虑了每一个选项
I've reconsidered every option.
这就是我的答案
And here's where I come out.
重来一次也一样
I would do it again.
因为迈克尔是我的兄弟  我要保护我的家人
Because Michael's my brother and I protect my family.
我知道
I know.
这正是他不解雇你的原因
And that's exactly why he won't fire you.
你有一张免罪卡  你只是使用了而已
You get one "get out of jail free" card and you just used it.
所以现在呢
So what now?
过来
Come here.
向前看  别在自责了
Now go forth and sin no more.
谢谢
Thanks.
为了什么  努力让你被解雇吗
For what? Trying to get you fired?
为了你一直在做正确的事
For always doing the right thing.
应该做的事
The right thing to do.
有时似乎不可能再看清真相了
Sometimes it seems impossible to know what that is anymore.
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
你的案件总结十分清楚表明邓恩先生包庇了他的儿子
Your case summary makes it perfectly clear that Mr. Dern covered for his son.
对他来说是努力保护自己的家人
In his mind, trying to protect his family.
尽管方法有误  但罪不至死
However misguided, I don't think anyone deserves to die for that.
我同意  先生
I agree, sir.
然而事实上  有一位联邦探员死亡了
But the fact remains there's a dead federal agent
凶手逍遥法外
whose murderer's walking the streets
因为邓恩选择妨碍司法公正
because Mr. Dern chose to obstruct justice.
他必须为此付出代价
And he has to pay for that.
但并不是性命
But not with his life.
所以你减缓了他的判决
So you're commuting his sentence.
是的  但没有减轻定罪
Yes, but not his conviction.
除非他说出真相  否则他会在监狱里度过余生
He'll spend his life in prison unless he tells the truth.
能帮我接通监狱吗  谢谢
Can you patch me through to the penitentiary? Thanks.
差点撞了你的车是一辆银色轿车
The car that nearly hit you was a silver sedan,
马里兰州牌照  开头是SK1
Maryland plates that start with SK1.
我把目标缩减到了19人
I narrowed it to 19 people.
你把这份名单和阿方索·朗交叉比对过吗
Did you cross-reference this list for connections to Alfonso Lang?
比对过了  没有发现
Yeah. Nothing.
圣卢西亚联邦银行呢
What about the Federal Bank of St. Lucia?
也搜索过了  没有
Ran that search, too.  Nada.
我会进行深层搜索
I'll run a deeper search.
看看这些人和伊卡洛斯跟劳埃德之间有没有哪怕是间接联系
Look for even tangential contacts between these people and Icarus, Lloyd.
19辆车可不是个小数目
Nineteen cars is a lot of cars.
的确是
Yeah. It's a lot of cars.
但想杀我的人肯定会确保
But the person who tried to kill me would wanna make sure
这辆车不会被追踪到他们
that this car wasn't traced back to them.
你知道这个名单的有趣之处在哪里吗
You know what's interesting about this list?
其中一辆车三天前发生了事故
One of the cars on it was in an accident three days ago.
- 你去哪  - 我有预感
- Where are you going? - I got a hunch.
如果我是对的  我就能知道是谁想杀我
If I'm right, I'll know who tried to kill me.
做得好伙计们  明天见
That's good work, boys. See you tomorrow.
威尔斯探员
Agent Wells.
我想你知道了你父亲的减刑
I assume you heard about your father's commutation.
我知道了  谢谢你的努力
I did. Thank you for all your work.
- 能减刑真是太好了  - 没错
- It's been a great relief. - I'm sure it is.
看着他为了你犯下的谋杀而死一定很糟
It would be terrible to watch him die for a murder you committed.
- 我不知道你在说什么  - 别装了
- I don't know what you're talking about. - Drop the act.
你我都清楚你永远不会承认
We both know you're never going to answer for it.
但你总要负责的
But you will answer for something.
- 你大错特错了  - 不 错的是你
-You're making a big mistake. -No, you did.
你试图用在你店里维修的车杀掉我
When you used a car that your shop was repairing to try and kill me.
我们知道开车的是你  你的办公室经理看见你上车了
We know you were driving the car. Your office manager saw you get into it.
- 她看错了  - 举起手来
- She's mistaken. - Put your hands up.
放在车上  立刻
On the car. Now!
救你父亲就意味着我会毁掉你的名声
Saving your dad meant that I would ruin your reputation,
所以你试着阻止我  猜猜怎么着
so you tried to run me down. Guess what?
虽然过了16年  但你最终还是要进监狱  混蛋
It's been 16 years, but you're finally going to jail, you son of a bitch.
第一夫人来了
I have the First Lady for you.
谢谢  艾娃  我正要回去
Thank you, Ava. Hey. I was just heading up to the Residence.
这不能等  你一定要解雇约翰·弗斯特
This couldn't wait. You need to fire John Foerstel.
- 为什么  - 因为他
- Why? - Because he is using his office
以权谋私
to create headlines for himself.
他为了潜在的政治利益而故意把水搅浑
He's purposely muddying the waters for potential political gain.
他背叛了职务誓言  这就是原因
He's betraying his oath of office, that is why.
- 艾利克斯  事情没有那么简单  - 不  就是这么简单
- Alex, it's not that easy. - Yes, it is.
帕特里克·劳埃德已经死了两个月
Patrick Lloyd has been dead for two months.
我们还在被他纠缠不休
We are still being haunted by him.
虚构的银行账户
The fabricated bank account.
根本不存在的伊卡洛斯的阴谋
The conspiracy with Icarus that doesn't even exist.
- 这些都不是真的  - 我知道
- None of this is real. - I know.
当你能有所作为时
Why are you letting us get dragged down by an investigation
你为什么还要让我们被调查拖累
when you can do something about it?
我的工作人员们想要我任命一名特别检察官
My staff wants me to appoint a special prosecutor.
你想让我解雇弗斯特
You want me to fire Foerstel.
- 你们都错过了关键  - 什么关键
- You're all missing the point. - What is the point?
你妈妈犯了联邦重罪
Your mother committed a federal crime.
可能在三十年前
Thirty years ago, maybe,
但她犯了罪  就会有后果
but she committed a crime. There are consequences.
我不能为了配合我们自己就去改变规则
I can't just change the rules because it suits us.
约翰·弗斯特准备竞选参议院
John Foerstel is preparing to run for Senate.
他违反了规则
He is not playing by the rules.
是的  见鬼  他违规了
Yes, he is, damn it!
也许不是我们期望的方式  但他只是在做自己的工作
He's doing his job, maybe not the way we want him to.
我不能因此就解雇他  如果我那么做了  我又成了什么人呢
I can't fire him for that. If I did, who would I be?
这就是我的丈夫
My husband.
真不敢相信你竟然那么说
I can't believe you just said that.
你质疑我作为丈夫的的承诺
You're questioning my commitment as a husband
就因为我在一切正确时
because I won't interfere in an investigation
不愿意干扰调查
where we've done absolutely nothing wrong?
艾利克斯  你是个杰出的律师  却是个糟糕的被告
You're a hell of a lawyer, Alex, but you're a lousy defendant.
- 再来些酒吗  - 好的
- More wine? - Sure.
- 都喝完了吗  - 是的
- Are we out? - Yep.
半夜还在努力工作吗  查克
Burning the midnight oil, Chuck?
是的  听着  我查了朗的手机  发现了一些东西
Yes, listen, I got something. I ran Lang's cell phone.
你是对的  有人在你去他的公寓前
You were right. Somebody called him right before you got to his condo.
- 用刻录机电话给他打了电话  - 知道是谁吗
- From a burner. - Do we know who it was?
不清楚  但我用三角定位法找到了发出信号的手机基站
No. But I triangulated the signal based on the cell phone towers.
在第四大道和H街交汇处  下午两点二十二分
Call came from 4th and H, 2:22 p.m.
我要去下卫生间  到时见
I'm gonna hit the loo. I'll meet you there.
汉娜  你还在吗
Hannah. Are you there?
还在  谢谢  查克  回头再说
Yeah. Thanks, Chuck, I'll talk to you soon.
接下来呢  你要去工作还是和我寻欢作乐
Hey, what's it gonna be? Work or pleasure?
和你开心下吧
Pleasure.
■
人人视频APP
在线观看美剧
离线高清缓存
更有海量高清电影
扫码即刻下载
特别推荐
■
各大应用市场均可下载
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
另：招募长期居住加拿大、美国的童鞋帮忙录制CC字幕（有偿）
联系QQ：864413459   请注明：CC录制